Another interesting game will be make money, it's another interesting extension is make
money, 200,000, very simple one, and a simple cooking game when you try to earn as much
money as possible.
How rich can you get?
So you see the income and the money.
I can test it out, so the economical games, that's the income, I'm great, so I'm not
the fourth in a month, click on updates, so it was not ready for CCLP still on a resource,
but it says locally some stuff, you're extremely poor, you're very poor, but now we are
about the poverty line, probably 100 will give us something, oh, still not, it's like
an income now, and upgrades I can go to a bust, and there's even a casino, okay, first
I will just use the mode, what features this extension has, what features are in this
extension, and open new agents, what are the most top five popular game-blank online types,
you see the features, click in mechanics, income system, so it can reset progression, okay,
so it's a botting, which ones can be simply add it to a Chrome extension for fake currency
simulation, and open new agent now after this features makes money, I can change to the
remote, in the context, or the plan, prepare, plan to implement those core gameplay features,
now you prepare the moves, enough to bring the moves, we can actually follow along with
I prefer this way, obviously we can ask agent, but first it will just plan, and we have
it on the magnum file on the right, we see here, okay, we have this popular file, okay,
okay, we will create those top three implements, so I can copy, and I can as well maybe add
something, making mechanism, restor system, have it, then casino system up, and to implement
it, now I will press build, pause the video, there will actually be a 9 to lose, but if
it will ignore, okay, I see now 2, 10, so no great, this is not implemented, but after
that I will add it, because you have to model them properly with the extension, because
it's like a headline, but in the meantime obviously you can try to play with this application
or even go to just for fun category, and go crumb, and see actually what sells, so we can
filter by most highest rated, we see crumb, piano, simulation, piano, and microsoft, so it
her, some fidget spinner, pretty simple, but people still like it, they play clicker balls,
these very can gather some users, with three results, and I create this with the total list,
but I was sure probably used that the simple iteration, so this you simply meant, see the
implement of free, I will copy it over, and I will change between ask an Azure mode, implement,
and casino tab, with these games, but you now add it, in the meantime we see it actually
created all of it, but before I load, I will wait for a proper online gambling times,
it creates internally to do six, so even if you say it's automatically created, and to
do this for it, and obviously in the previous prompt, they ask for icons, but still remember
there is a possibility if you don't want to add icons manually, so you can update the
minestreamficon references, the extension log without an icon files, so we can specify it in
the very very beginning when you created the list, so now if I pin the game, blink, clicker,
we see click to earn, and as you can see, it's actually clicking, we see even shop with
some better cursor, a byte, and now I can get more, right, so there's a prestige, we can
get like a power clicker gain, so now I get more, and there's some even casino when I can
spin, pretty addicting I would say, and when this time we have still money to play spin,
it's actually the acting, to scratch here, bicard, nothing, I would play roulette, I would
play not enough money, we need to work later with, and now we just put, I'm like 20, wow,
I won 14, that's awesome, so this way we can actually create a gambling clicker, we can
write a new feature to that, so for the first few prompts, I'm really excited, I would
like to make it more concise, so the click is here, the stats are here, but casino will
be a new tab, so before I end up, please add the casino as a new tab at the top, sample
shop, and same for main clicker, because now it's too long, particularly.
Okay, so now it should be updated, I will reload it, and now I will just try to open
it up, I will open gambling clicker, I can pin it, I see shop, I see casino, and now I can
gamble refest by cursor, click again, and the spin, scratch, we can actually try to scratch
more of it, there is roulette, I can put all of red, and gamble, I watch an ALOST, there's
a better cursor, and there's some prestige, I'm not sure what the boy is the prestige,
but we can remove it, remove prestige tab, but total, and it should be statistic, it should
be very, should be moved to stats, and below stats, should add a copyright, and make it
better, and then we have a money, but below average, certain, country, or enough, somebody, some
country, money, statistics, and open your agent, and money, add specifics when we click,
to earn, and get money, as the facts for shop improvements, and for free casino games.
It will now add some manager, integrate sound effects into a game, we see the list of 6 to
do, create sound manager with web audio API for generating sound effects, add clicks on
the effects when clicking to earn money, add practices sound effect to shop improvements,
and you have a for slots game XP in Windows and some effects for scratch and card game,
select scratch windows, and apply the new agent, I want to make scratch game more enjoyable,
so we can just paint with mouse or mouse, and discover a number slowly, refresh it, open
it again, perfect sound, let me hear golden cursor, perfect another one, let me play casino,
I really like the treasure style, there is a stretch cryo bye, oh my god that's so comfortable,
and we have a let us go, I hope put on green everything, okay and I lost it, but perfect,
I really love it, actually I'm thinking of releasing this extension for myself, you could
buy a nice meal, it didn't develop in country, maybe I would just remove from my name,
I think it's no point this, so you're any question, meaning opportunities, you could
buy a smartphone, a very old one, that's perfect, and maybe I would just remove my copyright,
so please remove, please make a quotation for you could buy a smartphone, another text,
a little bit smaller outline, because I want to have it in one top size, I need to scroll
now, okay now we upload it, let me see, okay it's nice,
although we could probably add a little bit bigger, so on the main one it's a statistics
shop casino, and we probably could adjust the shop to make it more feel, try to make
it feel to fit current size of the window and shop top could probably, has more displayed
because it's close, starts, early on Chrome, extension, window size, so I can say, now it's
completely wrong, I have to go again, reveal it, pull it up, probably, and we can do,
try to make a reverse, so I'll just redo the check point,
make a window size, feet, main deck, and now I'll just make a screen shut, and
mouse, mouse, mouse, mouse, mouse, mouse, mouse.
Even though we can try to see some of the errors, I can make it, maybe check it, so this
is the canvas to the operation, I can clear it all, and then I want to upload and see if
you get the same error after that prompt is finished, it's now updated, or reload, no errors
now, and now it fits well, alright, I just don't like that, it doesn't have the same size
as others, so, and main tab is fits well, other shop in casino should have the same size,
so it will not stretch, minus switching, depth, and we'll roll with the last prompt and it
should be good, the prompt means I didn't still see that scroll all the time, so I'll just
go back, push, and it's off here, so now we can click, shop, buy some cursors, click
casino, let's scratch, and play rot, okay, great, I like that app, and we can even fix
some errors, so if I have like an error, I can copy it over here, and then to be fixed,
I might add the initial refrigeration in one of the next videos.